Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is chunky monkey. Let me show you
how to make it. Of course, we're
starting off with a banana base. So,
we're using one small banana with some
fat-free high protein milk, sweetener,
salt, zantham gum, and a little bit of
vanilla bean paste. And as I say that,
I'm realizing I didn't film the vanilla
bean paste going in, but trust me, it's
in there. We're going to blend all those
ingredients together. Throw it in the
freezer for 16 hours at least and then
take it out, run under hot water for 30
seconds to a minute, and then throw it
in your creamy on the ice cream setting.
Eli, why why are you not using the light
ice cream setting? You use the light ice
cream setting for every single recipe. I
know, but of course, I tested this and I
realized that the banana actually adds a
good amount of starch, which thickens
your base, so you don't need to spin as
long. Pro tip, take the bowl that you
use to melt your chocolate, get a little
bit of ice cream,
And as always, full recipe is in the
description.